Hello
I am Chef Kilian!
I've been working in the restaurant industry for nine years.
I am currently the sous-chef at the michelin starred restaurant
Unpeeled Toaster?
located in the Stockholm port.
We do... French... Swedish... fusion food...
No, that does not mean Meatballs-Baguettes!
We focus mostly on shellfish.
And today I'm supposed to show you how to make a traditional french crab dish
called "Crabe à la Pep-Maximum"
which in english translates to
C R A B
I N
P E P S I
M A X
This is an old frankish recipe I learned
when I was in Paris looking for new tastes.
And a guy in this alley told me to try these
"locally grown mushrooms."
And, believe it or not, ten minutes later
I met a talking rat.
Which would seem odd
if it hadn't been for a classic movie warning me
this could happen.
It was the rat who told me of this holy combination!
The ingredients you will need is
a crab, and, ahhhh...
Pepsi Max
and Love! :-)
The crab, like this one,
should be grown in your home aquarium
They should also be served fresh
like this one would be, if I knew how to keep them alive...
I'm a chef, not a marine biologist!
It's been dead for 69 hours... ·-·
STEP ONE!
Make the main course.
Take out un casserole, I'm not sure what they are called in english...
Is... Is this an ovenmitt ?
Now pour the Pepsi:
You need about three Liters
(Or three gallons, which is american for "Liters")
You'll want to put the crab in cold Pepsi
If it's boiling, the shock of the heat might bring the crab back to life and it will chop off your nose!
Now, boil that, until you get bored of boiling it...
Step one is le finished, let's move onto Step Two!
Because it's french food, we will need to make the
B A G U E T T E
The ingredients you will need is
liquid ice and grinded wheat.
Ice is, fairly easy to melt, you put it in a form and throw it in the oven at 100° for ten minutes.
Tadaa!
Drinkable, and quite tasty.
Grinded wheat is... harder...
First you'll need a sickle, maybe you know a former communist that can sell you one.
Now go out and cut down some wheat
Then take the wheat to a windmill and grind it
And, Tadaa 2!
Put both of these things into a bowl, and that's how you get raw bread.
Then beat the raw bread into this shape
No, it's not to small, silly, this is how all B A G U E T T E looks like before the final most important step.
Making the cuts.
Then you will put it in the oven Upside Down!
And, as hot air rises
it will go in, through the cuts and expand the bread like a baloon.
And that's why they are so long
Let's check on the crab...
Mhhhh
Smells like...
drinking coffee, on a beautiful Paris morning
then Napoleon shows up and recuits you into his army.
Then you die somewhere in germany.
That's what this smells like
dying in mud.
But it reminds me, we are eating fish, so it obviously needs to be complemented
with some french white wine.
But I only have american red wine.
Serving red wine to fish...
Ahh Guillotine. No trial, just head off!
Do I have to go to the wine store ?
No. You can actually turn Red wine into White wine at home!
All you need to do is: Mix the red wine with turkish joghurt.
And it should give it that nice, white color.
And because we used american wine,
and turkish yoghurt
and france is between those two countries, it turns into
French White wine!
Take out the crab...
Carefully open the baguette...
Now gently place the crab inside the baguette...
Le perfection!
And finally, you need a candle from Notre Dame...
I stole one two weeks ago.
May have flipped over some other candles in the process...
But the fire department got there quick, so no worries!
And that, is Crabe à la Pep Maximum!
Sigh...
Look...
I get, my sublime cooking skills might... scare you off.
But I've had years of training
and that has guided me towards perfection.
A great chef once said:
"Where's the fucking lamb sauce?"
But a greater chef once said:
"Only artists are allowed to put trashbags on plates and call it great art,"
"We don't have that luxury."
"Our art takes years of blood, sweat and tears"
"that needs to stay out of every dish."
"Eventually, after days of shouting and carrying pots your throat will be dry and your hands not so beautiful."
"But you food... Ahhh your food will be the opposite!"
"And only then, can you call what you make"
"Great Art."
"Like I do" -Chef Kilian.